Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، وذبل إلى أشلاء♪
♪Yet I still can't find a trace of you♪
♪ومع ذلك، ما زلتُ لا أجد لك أثراً♪
♪Like a whale drowning in the cracks of the deep sea♪
♪كحوت يغرق في شقوق أعماق البحر♪
♪Thinking of you, I lose myself completely♪
♪أفكر فيك، فأفقد نفسي تماماً♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، وذبل إلى أشلاء♪
♪Humbly, I still long to search for you♪
بكل تواضع، ما زلت أتوق للبحث عنك.
♪Screaming as I fall into the darkest abyss♪
أصرخ وأنا أسقط في أحلك هاوية.
♪Echoing back is only the tide of loneliness♪
♪صدى الصوت ليس إلا موجة الوحدة♪
♪Overestimating myself♪
♪أبالغ في تقدير نفسي♪
=Marry Him in Her Place=
=تزوجيه مكانها=
=Episode 24=
=الحلقة 24=
Who goes there?
من يذهب إلى هناك؟
I, Liang Yi of Chengyun Society﻿, have come with my men to greet Staff Officer Wang.
أنا، ليانغ يي من جمعية تشنغيون، جئت مع رجالي لتحية الضابط وانغ.
So it's you, Mrs. Lin.
إذن أنتِ يا سيدتي لين.
What brings the lady of Chengyun Society
ما الذي يجلب سيدة جمعية تشنغيون؟
to a staff officer of Yunzhou?
إلى ضابط أركان في يونتشو؟
I have a business opportunity I'd like to discuss with you.
لدي فرصة عمل أود مناقشتها معك.
What business could a military officer like me
ما العمل الذي يمكن أن يقوم به ضابط عسكري مثلي؟
possibly negotiate with you?
هل من الممكن التفاوض معك؟
One that could set you up for life.
واحدة قد تؤمّن لك مستقبلاً زاهراً.
Go on.
هيا.
I'll be straight with you.
سأكون صريحاً معك.
You came a long way in a hurry.
لقد قطعت شوطاً طويلاً على عجل.
That can't have been easy.
لا بد أن ذلك لم يكن سهلاً.
Soon, you'll be back on the battlefield risking your neck.
قريباً، ستعود إلى ساحة المعركة وتخاطر بحياتك.
You bleed for the cause.
أنت تضحي بحياتك من أجل القضية.
But, he, Song Ming, reaps all the rewards.
لكن هو، سونغ مينغ، يحصد كل المكافآت.
If fate turns on you,
إذا انقلبت عليك الأقدار،
there'll always be
سيكون هناك دائماً
another Staff Officer Zhang or Staff Officer Li to take your place.
ضابط أركان آخر، تشانغ أو ضابط أركان آخر، ليحل محلك.
You're getting the short end of the stick.
أنت الخاسر في هذه المسألة.
So, what do you think
إذن، ما رأيك؟
I should do?
ماذا أفعل؟
Join hands with Chengyun Society.
انضموا إلى جمعية تشنغيون.
Once we succeed, Yunzhou will be yours.
بمجرد أن ننجح، ستكون يونتشو ملكك.
Jiangzhou will be mine.
ستكون جيانغتشو ملكي.
We rule together
نحن نحكم معاً
and keep it that way.
وحافظ على ذلك.
You really are the daughter of a merchant family.
أنتِ حقاً ابنة عائلة تجارية.
You have quite a talent for sizing things up.
لديك موهبة كبيرة في تقييم الأمور.
I wonder what your father-in-law would say
أتساءل ماذا سيقول والد زوجتك
if he heard this,
إذا سمع هذا،
Young Madam Song.
أغنية السيدة الشابة.
How fascinating.
يا له من أمر مثير للاهتمام.
Instead of keeping vigil
بدلاً من البقاء في حالة تأهب
at the Song Residence,
في مقر إقامة سونغ،
you're here plotting the future of the provinces.
أنت هنا تخطط لمستقبل المقاطعات.
That was
كان ذلك
a clever plan,
خطة ذكية،
I'll give you that.
أوافقك الرأي في ذلك.
If Governor Song hadn't made arrangements in advance,
لو لم يكن الحاكم سونغ قد اتخذ الترتيبات مسبقاً،
you might really have overturned Rong City today.
ربما تكون قد قلبت مدينة رونغ رأساً على عقب اليوم.
Men, seize her.
أيها الرجال، أمسكوا بها.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
(Rong City Municipal Hall, Rong City Police Bureau)
(مبنى بلدية مدينة رونغ، مكتب شرطة مدينة رونغ)
Staff Officer Wang, thank you for coming all this way.
أيها الضابط وانغ، شكراً لك على قدومك من كل هذه المسافة.
If this works out, I'll reward you well.
إذا نجح هذا الأمر، فسأكافئك جيداً.
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
I've overlooked your mistakes time and time again
لقد تغاضيت عن أخطائك مراراً وتكراراً
for your father's sake.
من أجل والدك.
Yet, you insist on defying me.
ومع ذلك، تصر على تحديّني.
To think
أن تفكر
you'd be as foolish as that spineless father of yours.
ستكون أحمق مثل والدك عديم الشخصية.
Don't blame me for removing an obstacle.
لا تلومني على إزالة العقبة.
You killed my father.
لقد قتلت أبي.
I did.
فعلتُ.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You really believe you can fight me when you are already cornered?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنك تستطيع قتالي وأنت محاصر بالفعل؟
My father did nothing to you.
لم يفعل لك والدي شيئاً.
He overreached.
لقد بالغ في تقدير الأمور.
He insisted on investigating the opium trade.
وأصر على التحقيق في تجارة الأفيون.
(Liang's Apothecary Ledger)
(سجل ليانغ للصيدلية)
Song Ming, look at what your son's gotten into!
سونغ مينغ، انظر إلى ما تورط فيه ابنك!
I never imagined that fool would dare touch opium.
لم أتخيل أبداً أن ذلك الأحمق سيجرؤ على لمس الأفيون.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
I'll deal with him once this is over.
سأتعامل معه حالما ينتهي هذا الأمر.
Once this is over?
بمجرد انتهاء هذا؟
Don't forget this.
لا تنس هذا.
When Rong City banned opium,
عندما حظرت مدينة رونغ الأفيون،
you led the charge.
لقد كنتَ قائد الهجوم.
And now you want to cover for your son?
والآن تريدين التستر على ابنك؟
Rest assured, I won't protect him in this.
اطمئن، لن أحميه في هذا الأمر.
But it is our children's wedding day.
لكن اليوم هو يوم زفاف أطفالنا.
You can consider this day never happened.
يمكنك اعتبار هذا اليوم وكأنه لم يحدث قط.
The wedding is off!
تم إلغاء الزفاف!
Liang, don't be rash.
ليانغ، لا تتسرع.
Your daughter is so fond of Zhichu.
ابنتك مغرمة جداً بزيتشو.
I won't let my Yi
لن أدع يي خاصتي
marry a man with no integrity.
تزوجي رجلاً بلا نزاهة.
You opposed me,
لقد عارضتني،
so you must suffer the consequences.
لذا عليك أن تتحمل العواقب.
Adjutant!
مساعد!
(Righteous Spirit)
(الروح الصالحة)
Bring him back to the Liang Residence.
أعده إلى مقر إقامة ليانغ.
Have Zhichu take care of him.
دع تشيتشو يعتني به.
Say the head of the Liang family got drunk
لنفترض أن رب أسرة ليانغ قد ثمل
on his daughter's wedding night,
في ليلة زفاف ابنته،
fell into the well,
سقط في البئر،
and died by accident.
وتوفي في حادث.
My father trusted you!
والدي كان يثق بك!
You and your son are monsters!
أنت وابنك وحوش!
Liang Yi, you're an impressive opponent.
ليانغ يي، أنت خصم مثير للإعجاب.
You married both my sons,
تزوجتِ كلا ولديّ،
set them against each other,
قم بتحريضهم ضد بعضهم البعض،
and got Zhichu killed.
وتسبب في مقتل زيتشو.
But you won't live beyond today.
لكنك لن تعيش بعد اليوم.
Yun.
هذا كل شيء.
Everything I have worked for is about to fall into place.
كل ما عملت من أجله على وشك أن يتحقق.
The only rift between us is that wretched woman.
الخلاف الوحيد بيننا هو تلك المرأة البائسة.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
I'll give you a chance.
سأمنحك فرصة.
Kill her yourself,
اقتلها بنفسك،
and all your past deeds
وكل أعمالك السابقة
will be forgiven.
سيتم التسامح.
From this moment on, you'll be the only son of the Song family,
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدًا، ستكون الابن الوحيد لعائلة سونغ،
the only young marshal of Jiangzhou.
المارشال الشاب الوحيد في جيانغتشو.
Do it.
افعلها.
Staff Officer Wang, what is the meaning of this?
الضابط وانغ، ما معنى هذا؟
I've decided to switch my allegiances.
لقد قررت تغيير ولائي.
If Governor Song hadn't made arrangements in advance,
لو لم يكن الحاكم سونغ قد اتخذ الترتيبات مسبقاً،
you might really have overturned Rong City today.
ربما تكون قد قلبت مدينة رونغ رأساً على عقب اليوم.
Men.
الرجال.
Seize her.
اقبضوا عليها.
Mrs. Lin!
السيدة لين!
All of you, stop!
توقفوا جميعاً!
To think this pack of vermin managed to slip into Jiangzhou.
يا للعجب أن تتمكن هذه المجموعة من الحشرات من التسلل إلى جيانغتشو.
Seize them!
اقبضوا عليهم!
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Wait.
انتظر.
I have one request.
لدي طلب واحد.
You think you have what it takes to revolt?
أتظن أن لديك ما يلزم للثورة؟
Allow me to enlighten you.
اسمح لي أن أوضح لك الأمر.
Commander Jin has already surrounded your men.
لقد حاصر القائد جين رجالكم بالفعل.
Miss Liang, I'll send him on his way now.
آنسة ليانغ، سأسمح له بالانصراف الآن.
Yun, I'm your father!
يون، أنا والدك!
Father?
أب؟
You don't deserve that title.
أنت لا تستحق هذا اللقب.
You think I don't know
أتظن أنني لا أعرف؟
you ordered Song Zhichu's mother to beat my mother and me to death
لقد أمرت والدة سونغ تشيتشو بضرب أمي وأنا حتى الموت
because you hated that my mother was a servant?
لأنك كنت تكره أن تكون أمي خادمة؟
She's dead. She won't give you any more trouble.
لقد ماتت. لن تسبب لك أي متاعب أخرى.
A servant
خادم
dreaming she could use a child to threaten me.
كانت تحلم بأنها تستطيع استخدام طفل لتهديدي.
Pathetic.
مثير للشفقة.
I thought
ظننت
you went after Zhichu
لقد ذهبت وراء تشيتشو
because his mother killed yours.
لأن أمه قتلت أمك.
Turns out I was the real target.
اتضح أنني كنت الهدف الحقيقي.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I got close to him so I could investigate you.
لقد اقتربت منه حتى أتمكن من التحقيق معك.
I want the Song family gone from Rong City once and for all.
أريد أن ترحل عائلة سونغ من مدينة رونغ نهائياً.
Staff Officer Wang.
الضابط وانغ.
He's not worth dirtying your hands.
إنه لا يستحق أن تلطخ يديك به.
This is the only courtesy you'll get from me.
هذا هو اللطف الوحيد الذي ستحصل عليه مني.
Do it yourself.
افعل ذلك بنفسك.
Let's go home.
هيا بنا إلى المنزل.
Why are you hiding?
لماذا تختبئ؟
You're bullying me again.
أنت تتنمر عليّ مجدداً.
Who's bullying you?
من الذي يتنمر عليك؟
You.
أنت.
Did I bully you?
هل تنمرت عليك؟
Nonsense.
هراء.
♪Walking together for so long♪
♪نسير معاً منذ زمن طويل♪
♪When we met again, snow was settling on our shoulders♪
♪عندما التقينا مجدداً، كان الثلج يتساقط على أكتافنا♪
♪I never thought that in this moment too♪
♪لم يخطر ببالي ذلك في هذه اللحظة أيضاً♪
♪We'd get a brief taste of growing old together♪
♪سنتذوق قليلاً طعم الشيخوخة معاً♪
♪Yet we can't hold each other or stay together anymore♪
♪لكننا لم نعد قادرين على احتضان بعضنا البعض أو البقاء معًا♪
♪We missed each other in the snowfall♪
♪اشتقنا لبعضنا البعض في تساقط الثلج♪
♪Every step, another glance back, but never stopping♪
♪كل خطوة، نظرة أخرى إلى الوراء، لكن دون توقف♪
♪The drifting snow brushed past our sleeves♪
♪ لامست الثلوج المتراكمة أكمامنا ♪
♪Smoothing your frown for me♪
♪أزيل عبوسك من أجلي♪
♪We parted ways at the crossroads of snow♪
♪افترقنا عند مفترق طرق الثلج♪
♪We loved deeply, yet had to let go♪
♪أحببنا بشدة، لكن كان علينا أن نتخلى♪
♪Let the snow drown the weight of our steps♪
♪دع الثلج يغمر ثقل خطواتنا♪
♪And bury the quivering hurt along with them♪
♪ وادفن الألم المرتجف معهم ♪
You're up.
دورك الآن.
What's all this?
ما هذا كله؟
Cakes.
الكعك.
I didn't know what you liked
لم أكن أعرف ما الذي يعجبك
so I bought two.
لذلك اشتريت اثنين.
And you bought two identical ones?
واشتريت اثنين متطابقين؟
Are you teasing me?
هل تمازحني؟
♪Between the lines of words♪
♪بين سطور الكلمات♪
♪Telling fragments of love and sorrow♪
♪أروي شذرات من الحب والحزن♪
♪Sun, moon, and stars♪
♪الشمس والقمر والنجوم♪
♪Speak not, for it is longing♪
لا تتكلم، فهذا شوق
♪Loneliness sealed in dust♪
♪وحدةٌ محصورةٌ في الغبار♪
♪The longer it stays, the deeper it grows♪
كلما طالت مدة بقائه، كلما ازداد عمقه
♪Seeing through all worldly things♪
♪رؤية ما وراء كل الأشياء الدنيوية♪
♪All sorrow fades into nothingness♪
♪كل الحزن يتلاشى في العدم♪
♪My beloved is without fault♪
♪حبيبي بلا عيب♪
♪To understand is already so rare♪
♪إن الفهم أصبح نادراً جداً♪
♪Holding tight to what's not yours♪
♪التمسك بشدة بما ليس لك♪
(With the help of Marshal Jin, Liang Yi and Lin Yun﻿)
(بمساعدة مارشال جين، ليانغ يي، ولين يون)
(eliminated Song Ming and his remaining forces, preventing Rong City﻿ from falling into chaos.)
(تم القضاء على سونغ مينغ وقواته المتبقية، مما منع مدينة رونغ من السقوط في الفوضى.)
(Liang Yi became head of the Rong City Chamber of Commerce.)
(أصبح ليانغ يي رئيسًا لغرفة تجارة مدينة رونغ.)
(Lin Yun dissolved Chengyun Society and donated all his assets to rebuild the city.)
(قام لين يون بحل جمعية تشنغيون وتبرع بجميع أصوله لإعادة بناء المدينة.)
I'm a busy woman.
أنا امرأة مشغولة.
Don't be so clingy.
لا تكن شديد التشبث.
Lin Yun, put me down!
لين يون، أنزلني!
Put me down!
أنزلني!
(Be brave, braver than you have ever been.)
(كن شجاعاً، أشجع مما كنت عليه من قبل.)
(Embrace what stirs your heart.)
(احتضن ما يثير مشاعرك.)
(Protect the connection that deserves to be cherished.)
(احمِ العلاقة التي تستحق أن تُعتز بها.)
(Be clumsy, stumble if you must,)
(كن أخرقاً، وتعثر إن لزم الأمر،)
(but love with sincerity and without reservation.)
(لكن الحب بصدق وبدون تحفظ.)
(May all who love find the courage to chase the stars and the sea.)
(ليجد كل من يحب الشجاعة لمطاردة النجوم والبحر.)
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪
♪ارفعوا الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأوا عرضكم المتكلف♪
♪The most foolish gambler♪
♪أغبى مقامر♪
♪Would treat love as prey, caring nothing♪
♪سيتعامل مع الحب كفريسة، ولا يبالي بشيء♪
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء لا تزال حاضرة في ذهني.
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪يا لها من هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪يُكشف عن النصر بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪عاملتني كدمية♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪ونسقط كلانا في عزلة لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪أحببتُ بعمقٍ شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
أساليبك قاسية للغاية
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لا ينتظرك إلا العار♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪عاملتني كدمية♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪ونسقط كلانا في عزلة لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪أحببتُ بعمقٍ شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
أساليبك قاسية للغاية
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لا ينتظرك إلا العار♪
♪Curtain call♪
♪نداء الستار♪